Harold Spivacke Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Correspondence, 1923-1984, undated, (8 boxes) (Box 5-11, 33)
  - Miller, Dayton C., 1931-1933 (Box-folder 9/7)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box-folder 9/8)
  - Music Advisory Panel see Photographs, Photoprints, Spivacke with others
  - "M" miscellaneous (Box-folder 9/9)
  - National Music Council, 1956-1972, undated see also Photographs, Photoprints, Spivacke with others; Printed Matter, Bulletins / Newsletters; Realia, National Music Council (Box-folder 9/10)
  - New York University, 1924-1929 (Box-folder 9/11)
  - New York University 50th Anniversary Reunion, 1970 (Box-folder 9/12)
  - "N" miscellaneous (Box-folder 9/13)
  - Oberdörffer, Fritz and Rose, 1933-1977, undated (Box-folder 9/14)
  - "O" miscellaneous (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Piatigorsky, Gregor, 1955 (Box-folder 10/2)
  - "P" miscellaneous (Box-folder 10/3)
  - Retirement album, 1972, undated (Box-folder 11/1)
  - Retirement correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Rhodes, Millard, 1962 (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Riemenschneider, Albert, 1947 see also Correspondence, Baldwin-Wallace College; Writings by others, Riemenschneider, Albert; Realia, Baldwin-Wallace College (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Roberts, Helen H., 1934-1936 (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Rome, Harold, 1963 (Box-folder 10/8)
  - Rothschild, Germaine de, 1960-1969, undated (Box-folder 7/11)
  - "R" miscellaneous (Box-folder 10/9)
  - Saminsky, Lazare, 1934 (Box-folder 10/10)
  - Santa Cruz, Domingo, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 10/11)
  - Schirmer, G., Inc. see Engel, Carl
  - Schoenberg, Gertrud, 1955 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Scholes, Percy A., 1957 (Box-folder 10/13)
  - Schuman, William, 1955-1972 (Box-folder 10/14)
  - Second International Congress of Parasitology see same entry under Realia
  - Seeger, Charles, 1935 (Box-folder 10/15)
  - Siegmeister, Elie and Hannah, 1969, undated (Box-folder 10/16)
  - Slonimsky, Nicolas, 1959-1962 (Box-folder 10/17)
  - Smith, Carleton Sprague, 1933-1955, undated (Box-folder 10/18)
  - Spivacke family, 1934-1972, undated (Box-folder 10/19)
  - State University of New York at Buffalo see Bradley, Carol June
  - Stern, Isaac, undated (Box-folder 10/20)
  - Stevenson, Robert, 1972-1975 see also Dallapiccola, Luigi and Laura and Retirement album (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Stokowski, Leopold, 1957-1963 (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Stravinsky, Igor, undated (Box-folder 10/23)
  - "S" miscellaneous (Box-folder 10/24)
  - "T" miscellaneous (Box-folder 10/25)
  - Unidentified (Box-folder 10/26)
  - University of Berlin, 1933-1965, undated (Box-folder 10/27)
  - University of Berlin, 1933 (Box-folder 33/3)
  - "U" miscellaneous (Box-folder 10/28)
  - Vega, Aurelio de la and Sarita de la Vega, 1958-1983, undated see also Retirement correspondence (Box-folder 7/10)
  - "V" miscellaneous (Box-folder 10/29)
  - War Department and Navy Department see same entry under Realia
  - Weitz, L., 1933 (Box-folder 10/30)
  - Whittall, Gertrude Clarke, 1955-1977, undated (Box-folder 10/31)
  - Woodworth, G. Wallace, 1933 (Box-folder 10/32)
  - "W" miscellaneous (Box-folder 10/33)
  - Yasser, Joseph, 1934, undated (Box-folder 10/34)
  - "Y" miscellaneous (Box-folder 10/35)
- Subject File, 1925-1977, undated, (1 box) (Box 12)
  Manuscript, typescript, and printed materials; manuscript and typescript letters; lists; typescript and printed programs; and clippings relating to biographical information, conferences, a demonstration with photographs, and White House inaugurations.
  Arranged alphabetically by subject and chronologically therein.
  - Biographical materials on Harold Spivacke, 1961-1977, undated (Box-folder 12/1)
  - Japanese music library tour, 1976-1977, undated (Box-folder 12/2)
  - Princeton University Bicentennial Conference, 1946 (Box-folder 12/3)
  - Princeton University Bicentennial Conference, 1947 (Box-folder 12/4)
  - RCA demonstration of Ultrafax with David Sarnoff, 1948 (Box-folder 12/5)
  - Shakespeare in North America, 400th anniversary, 1964 see also White House (Box-folder 12/6)
  - Spivacke Fund Collection, 1977, undated (Box-folder 12/7)
  - White House, 1960-1968 see also Shakespeare in North America, 400th anniversary (Box-folder 12/8)
  - Gertrude Clarke Whittall Foundation, 1925-1937, undated (Box-folder 12/9)
- Legal and Financial, 1923-1974, undated, (1 folder) (Box 13)
  Student passes from Germany, affidavit, applications, miscellaneous receipts, checkbook stubs, and other printed items.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Financial and legal, 1923-1974, undated (Box-folder 13/1)
- Programs, 1924-1984, undated, (3 boxes) (Box 13-14, 33)
  Typescript and printed programs.
  - 1924 (Box-folder 33/4)
  - 1924-1932 (Box-folder 13/2)
  - 1933-1947 (Box-folder 13/3)
  - 1953-1960 see also Realia, University of Rochester (Box-folder 13/4)
  - 1961-1963 (Box-folder 13/5)
  - 1964-1965 (Box-folder 13/6)
  - 1966-1968 (Box-folder 13/7)
  - 1970-1974 (Box-folder 14/1)
  - 1978-1984 (Box-folder 14/2)
  - Undated (Box-folder 14/3)
- Clippings, 1933-1984, (2 folders) (Box 14, 33)
  Newspaper clippings and magazine articles.
  - 1933-1984 (Box-folder 14/4)
  - 1972 Feb. 13, Sunday Star, Printing plate (Box-folder 33/5)
- Realia, 1923-1974, (3 boxes) (Box 27, 31-32)
  Certificates, earned and honorary degrees, medals, and plaques.
  Arranged alphabetically by presenter's name.
  - Acoustical Society of America membership certificates, 1932, 1957 (Box-folder 31/1)
  - Baldwin-Wallace College, Honorary Doctor of Music degree, 1947 see also Correspondence, Baldwin-Wallace College; Correspondence, Riemenschneider, Albert; Writings by others, Riemenschneider, Albert (Box-folder 31/2)
  - Cleveland Institute of Music, Honorary Doctor of Music degree, 1969 (Box-folder 31/3)
  - Department of State Cultural Presentations, medal, in black leather case, undated (Box-folder 27/1)
  - Elizabeth Sprague Coolidge, medal, in blue leather case, inscribed to Harold Spivacke on the occasion of the twentieth anniversary of the Berkshire Festival of Chamber Music, 1938 Sept. 23 (Box-folder 27/1)
  - Library of Congress distinguished service certificates and retirement certificate, 1965, 1970, 1972 (Box-folder 31/4)
  - Manuscript Society membership certificate, 1949 (Box-folder 31/5)
  - Metropolitan Washington Board of Trade certificate regarding Third Inter-American Music Festival, 1965 (Box-folder 31/6)
  - Music Library Association, Distinguished Service Citation, undated (Box-folder 31/7)
  - Music Teachers National Association membership certificate, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 31/8)
  - National Association for American Composers and Conductors, Outstanding Service Certificate, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 31/9)
  - National Music Council tribute certificate regarding thirty-fifth anniversary as chief of the Music Division, Library of Congress; also includes three photographs of Spivacke alone, 1972 Jan. 4 see also Correspondence, National Music Council; Photographs, Photoprints, Spivacke with others; Printed Matter, Bulletins / Newsletters (Box-folder 31/10)
  - New York University, Bachelor and Master of Arts degrees, 1923, 1924 (Box-folder 31/11)
  - Organization of American States plaques regarding Fifth and Sixth Inter-American Music Festival, 1971 May 20 and 1974 May (Box 32)
  - Phi Mu Alpha membership certificate, 1956 Jun. 3 (Box-folder 31/12)
  - Phi Sigma Delta certificate regarding twenty-five years of membership, 1953 Sept. (Box-folder 31/13)
  - Princeton University Bicentennial, two medals, two presentation cards, two printed descriptions, and name tag, 1946 (Box-folder 27/2)
  - Second International Congress of Parasitology appreciation certificate, 1970 Sept., Includes one letter dated May 3, 1971. (Box-folder 31/14)
  - Sigma Alpha Iota Certificate of Merit, undated (Box-folder 31/15)
  - Star-Spangled Banner Sesquicentennial, two medals in red leather case, 1814-1964 (Box-folder 27/3)
  - United States Army plaque in appreciation for All-Army Entertainment Contest, 1956 (Box 32)
  - University of Berlin, Doctor of Philosophy (Musikwissenschaft) degree, 1929 Oct. 29 (Box-folder 31/16)
  - University of Rochester, Honorary Doctor of Music degree, with presentation speech, two baccalaureate service programs, and two commencement programs, 1955 Jun. 12 see also Programs, 1953-1960 (Box-folder 31/17)
  - War Department and Navy Department certificate of appreciation, 1946 Apr. 15, Includes letter dated 1946 May 6. (Box-folder 31/18)
  - Who's Who in Government certificate of biographical record, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 31/19)
- Photographs, 1928-1975, undated, (11 boxes) (Box 17-26, 30)
  - Photoprints, All black and white and less than 8x10 in size unless noted otherwise; dates given when known. (Box 17-21, 23, 30)
    Black and white and color in various sizes, black and white and sepia contact sheets, and miscellaneous items including color slides, photocards, and one half-tone printing plate.
    Arranged by subject within category, then by size or by person's name in alphabetical order, and by size therein.
    - Harold Spivacke Alone
      - 8x10 (Box-folder 17/1)
      - Looseleaf album, 8x10 (Box-folder 20/1)
      - Miscellaneous sizes, some in color (Box-folder 17/2)
      - Miscellaneous sizes (Box-folder 21/1)
      - Miscellaneous sizes in color see also Realia, National Music Council (Box-folder 21/62)
    - Harold Spivacke with Others
      - Albrecht, Otto (Box-folder 17/3)
      - American Society of Composers, Authors, and Publishers (ASCAP), 8x10 and miscellaneous sizes (Box-folder 17/4)
      - Bloom, Fred see Lowens, Irving, and Fred Bloom
      - Chase, Gilbert (Box-folder 21/2)
      - Coolidge, Elizabeth S., 8x10 (Box-folder 17/5)
      - Coolidge, Elizabeth S., 11x13 (Box-folder 30/4)
      - Coolidge Conference (Box-folder 17/6)
      - Coolidge Festival, 1975 (Box-folder 17/7)
      - Hanson, Howard, 8x10 and miscellaneous sizes (Box-folder 17/8)
      - Horton, Frank, Signed 8x10 (Box-folder 17/9)
      - International Music Council, 1960 (Box-folder 17/10)
      - Johnson, President Lyndon and the First Lady, Lady Bird Johnson (Box-folder 30/5)
      - Khachaturian, Aram (Box-folder 17/11)
      - Korson, Rae (Box-folder 21/3)
      - Leavitt, Donald, and William Lichtenwanger (Box-folder 21/4)
      - Lichtenwanger, William see Leavitt, Donald, and William Lichtenwanger
      - Light, Enoch, Signed 8x10 (Box-folder 17/12)
      - Lowens, Irving, and Fred Bloom (Box-folder 21/5)
      - Miller, Philip (Box-folder 21/6)
      - Moore, Earl (Box-folder 21/7)
      - Music Advisory Panel, with two letters, 1962 (Box-folder 17/13)
      - Music Teachers National Association, 1952, 1955, undated (Box-folder 17/14)
      - National Music Council, 1972 see also Correspondence, National Music Council; Realia, National Music Council; Printed Matter, Bulletins / Newsletters (Box-folder 17/15)
      - Princess Irene of Greece (Box-folder 17/16)
      - Riemenschneider Bach Institute (note on verso), 1970 (Box-folder 17/17)
      - Rodgers, Mary (Box-folder 17/18)
      - Rome, Harold see Correspondence, Harold Rome
      - Saul, Patrick (Box-folder 21/8)
      - Texas State Library, 1966 (Box-folder 17/19)
      - Thieme, Darius (Box-folder 21/9)
      - Unidentified people, 8x10 (Box-folder 17/20)
      - Unidentified people, Looseleaf album, 8x10 (Box-folder 20/2)
      - Unidentified people, Two 7-1/2x9-1/2, mounted (Box-folder 30/6)
      - Unidentified people, Miscellaneous sizes (Box-folder 21/10)
      - Unidentified people, Miscellaneous sizes, in color (Box-folder 21/63)
      - United States Army, 1954, 1956 (Box-folder 17/21)
    - Harold and Rose Marie Spivacke
      - Looseleaf album, 8x10 (Box-folder 20/3)
      - Miscellaneous sizes (Box-folder 21/11)
    - Harold and Rose Marie Spivacke with Others
      - 8x10 (Box-folder 17/22)
      - Miscellaneous sizes (Box-folder 21/12)
      - Miscellaneous sizes, in color (Box-folder 21/64)
    - Rose Marie Spivacke Alone
      - 8x10 (Box-folder 17/23)
      - Looseleaf album, 8x10 (Box-folder 20/4)
      - Miscellaneous sizes (Box-folder 21/13)
    - Rose Marie Spivacke with Others
      - 8x10 (Box-folder 17/24)
      - Looseleaf album, 8x10 (Box-folder 20/5)
      - Miscellaneous sizes (Box-folder 21/14)
    - Other People
      - Albert, Eugen d' (Box-folder 21/25)
      - Albrecht, Otto, 5x7 (Box-folder 18/1)
      - Albrecht, Otto, Miscellaneous sizes (Box-folder 21/15)
      - Anglès, Higini (Box-folder 21/16)
      - Bang, Maia, 1935, 8x10, signed (Box-folder 18/2)
      - Baron, Herman (Box-folder 21/17)
      - Ben-Ami, Joseph, 8x10, one signed (Box-folder 18/3)
      - Boonin, Joseph (Box-folder 21/18)
      - Britten, Valentine (Box-folder 21/19)
      - Britton, Allen (Box-folder 21/20)
      - Budapest String Quartet, 8x10, two signed (Box-folder 18/4)
      - Buechner, Alan C. (Box-folder 21/21)
      - Carneal, Robert (Box-folder 21/22)
      - Chase, Gilbert (Box-folder 21/23)
      - Clarke, Henry Leland (Box-folder 21/24)
      - Dallapiccola, Luigi (Box-folder 21/26)
      - Dayton C. Miller Flute Collection, 1928 (Box-folder 21/27)
      - Downes, Olin, 8x10, signed (Box-folder 18/5)
      - Einstein, Albert and Alfred (Box-folder 21/28)
      - Elmer, Minnie (Box-folder 21/29)
      - Feist, Leonard (Box-folder 21/30)
      - Fox, Charles Warren (Box-folder 21/31)
      - Gershwin, Ira, 8x10 (Box-folder 18/6)
      - Ginastera, Alberto, 8x10 (Box-folder 18/7)
      - Ginastera, Alberto and Aurora, Color (Box-folder 21/65)
      - Grainger, Percy, 10-3/4x13-3/4, signed (Box-folder 30/7)
      - Halm, Heinrich (Box-folder 21/32)
      - Heckmann, Harald (Box-folder 21/33)
      - Heckmann, Harald, Folke Linberg, and Wolfgang Rehm see also Linberg, Folke and Rehm, Wolfgang, 8x10 (Box-folder 18/8)
      - Hill, Mr. and Mrs. Richard, Color (Box-folder 21/66)
      - Hood, Mantle (Box-folder 21/34)
      - Hume, Paul (Box-folder 21/35)
      - Kennedy, President and Mrs. John F. (Box-folder 18/9)
      - Kinkeldey, Otto, 8x10 and 4x5 (Box-folder 18/10)
      - Köhler, K. H. (Box-folder 21/36)
      - Le Fèvre, Carolyn see also same entry under Correspondence, 8x10, one signed by photographer (Box-folder 18/11)
      - Lesueur, François (Box-folder 21/37)
      - Linberg, Folke O. see also Heckmann, Harald, Folke Linberg, and Wolfgang Rehm (Box-folder 21/38)
      - London String Quartet (Box-folder 18/12)
      - Lund, Sven (Box-folder 21/39)
      - Merritt, A. Tillman (Box-folder 21/40)
      - Mitchell, William J. (Box-folder 21/41)
      - Moore, Earl see also Rose Marie Spivacke with Others (Box-folder 21/42)
      - Morin, Gosta (Box-folder 21/43)
      - Music Library Association National Convention (rolled), 1958 (Box-folder 22/90)
      - Noske, Fritz (Box-folder 21/44)
      - Plamenac, Dragan (Box-folder 21/45)
      - Quartetto Italiano (signed) (Box-folder 18/13)
      - Querol Gavaldá, Miguel (Box-folder 21/46)
      - Reese, Gustave (Box-folder 21/47)
      - Rehm, Wolfgang see also Heckmann, Harald, Folke Linberg, and Wolfgang Rehm (Box-folder 21/48)
      - Ryan, Milo, 8x10 (Box-folder 18/14)
      - Ryan, Milo, Miscellaneous sizes (Box-folder 21/49)
      - Saul, Patrick, 8x10 (Box-folder 18/15)
      - Saul, Patrick, 4x5 (Box-folder 21/50)
      - Schmidt-Phiseldeck, K. (Box-folder 21/51)
      - Schoenberg, Gertrud, 8x10 (Box-folder 18/16)
      - Schrade, Leo (Box-folder 21/52)
      - Seeger, Charles (Box-folder 21/53)
      - Serkin, Rudolf see also Unidentified performers in Coolidge Auditorium at Library of Congress (Box-folder 21/54)
      - Sonneck Society, Color (Box-folder 21/67)
      - Spivacke, Howard, 8x10 (Box-folder 18/17)
      - Spivacke, Robert C. (Box-folder 21/55)
      - Unidentified people, 8x10 (Box-folder 18/18-19)
      - Unidentified people, 8x10 (mounted) (Box-folder 30/8)
      - Unidentified people, 8x10, Looseleaf album (Box-folder 20/6)
      - Unidentified people, 5x7 (Box-folder 19/1)
      - Unidentified people, 4x5 (Box-folder 21/56)
      - Unidentified people, Miscellaneous sizes (Box-folder 21/57)
      - Unidentified people, Miscellaneous sizes, in color (Box-folder 21/68)
      - Unidentified performers, 8x10 (Box-folder 19/2)
      - Unidentified performers, 8x10, Looseleaf album (Box-folder 20/7)
      - Unidentified performers, Miscellaneous sizes (Box-folder 21/58)
      - Unidentified performers in Coolidge Auditorium at Library of Congress, 8x10 (Box-folder 19/3)
      - Unidentified performers in Coolidge Auditorium at Library of Congress, 8x10, Looseleaf album (Box-folder 20/8)
      - Warwick, [?], 8x10 (Box-folder 19/4)
      - Waters, Edward, 8x10 (Box-folder 19/5)
      - Waters, Edward, Miscellaneous sizes (Box-folder 21/59)
      - Waters, Lily, 8x10 (Box-folder 19/6)
      - Welch, Roy (Box-folder 19/7)
      - Whittall, Gertrude Clarke (Box-folder 19/8)
      - Zehntner, H. (Box-folder 21/60)
    - Scenery / Still Lifes
      - 8x10 (Box-folder 19/9)
      - 8x10, Looseleaf album (Box-folder 20/9)
      - Miscellaneous sizes (Box-folder 19/10)
      - Miscellaneous sizes (Box-folder 21/61)
      - Miscellaneous sizes, in color (Box-folder 21/69)
    - Albums
      - Die Alexander von Humboldt-Stiftung und Der Akademische Austauschdienst, 1929 (Box-folder 30/1)
      - Europe: Berlin, Brussels, Cladow, Darnstadt, Dresden, Grunewald, Hamburg, Havel, Heidelberg, Leipzig, Meissen, Mittenwald, Oberan, Potsdam, Sans Souci, Spreewald, 1929-1930 (Box-folder 30/2)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box-folder 30/3)
    - Contact Sheets, All black and white and 35mm unless noted otherwise; dates given when known.
      - Colorado, 1961 (Box-folder 23/1)
      - Europe: London, Greenwich, Basel (Hans Holbein, Schrade, Zehntner, von Hirsch), Berne, Ouchy / Lausanne, Mt. Blanc, Montreux, Lake Geneva, 1961, Also in 2-1/2x2-1/2 (Box-folder 23/2)
      - Europe: Florence, Milan, Rome, 1963 (Box-folder 23/3)
      - Europe, undated (Box-folder 23/4)
      - Harold and Rose Marie Spivacke, 1962, Also in 2-1/2x2-1/2 (Box-folder 23/5)
      - International Music Council, 1961 (Box-folder 23/6)
      - Milo Ryan / Skyline Drive, 1961 (Box-folder 23/7)
      - Miscellaneous, 35mm (Box-folder 23/8)
      - Miscellaneous, 2-1/2x2-1/2 (Box-folder 23/9)
      - Miscellaneous, Sepia, 35mm and 2-1/2x2/12 (Box-folder 23/10)
      - Miscellaneous, Black and white and Sepia, 35mm and 2-1/2x2-1/2 (rolled) (Box-folder 22/91)
      - Skyline Drive, 1961 Aug., Also in 2-1/2x2-1/2 (Box-folder 23/11)
      - Sylvia Vorheer / Skyline Drive, 1961 (Box-folder 23/12)
      - Unidentified performers, undated (Box-folder 23/13)
      - Unidentified performers in Coolidge Auditorium at Library of Congress, undated (Box-folder 23/14)
      - Winston Salem, 1962 (Box-folder 23/15)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Postcards (Box-folder 19/11)
      - Printing plate: Harold Spivacke (half-tone, positive) (Box-folder 22/89)
      - Slides: Guillermo Espinosa, Juan Orrego-Salas, Harold Spivacke, Harold and Rose Marie Spivacke, University of Rhode Island, Miscellaneous (Box-folder 19/12)
  - Negatives, All black and white and 35mm in size unless noted otherwise; dates given when known. (Box 22, 24-26)
    Black and white and sepia in 35mm, 2x2, and 3x5 sizes.
    Arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - Harold Spivacke Alone
      - Miscellaneous, 2x2 (Box-folder 22/1-9)
      - Miscellaneous, 3x5 (Box-folder 24/1-11)
    - Other People
      - Miscellaneous, 2x2 (Box-folder 22/10-44)
      - Miscellaneous, 3x5 (Box-folder 24/12-47)
    - Scenery
      - Florence, 1963 (Box-folder 26/89-94)
      - Rome, 1963 (Box-folder 26/95-100)
      - Roman Forum, 1963 (Box-folder 26/101-106)
      - Miscellaneous, 2x2 (Box-folder 22/45-88)
      - Miscellaneous, 3x5 (Box-folder 24/48-138)
      - Unidentified (Box-folder 25/1-122)
      - Unidentified (Box-folder 26/1-88)
- Artwork, 1927-1947, undated, (1 box) (Box 29)
  Pencil, charcoal, and watercolor drawings, a silhouette, and reproductions.
  Arranged alphabetically by artist's name.
  - Aronson, Arthur, 1934 June 26, Pencil sketch (Box-folder 29/1)
  - Beline, George, 1929, Charcoal drawing (Box-folder 29/2)
  - Beline, George, 1927, Reproduction of charcoal drawing (Box-folder 29/2)
  - Coolidge, Elizabeth Sprague, 1947, Three watercolors (Box-folder 29/3)
  - Mochi, Ugo, undated, Paper silhouette (Box-folder 29/4)
  - Reproductions, undated, One annotated and one signed. (Box-folder 29/5)
- Music, 1943-1971, undated, (2 boxes) (Box 28, 33)
  Printed and manuscript music.
  Arranged alphabetically by composer and by title therein.
  - Army Service Forces. Hymns from home. [S.l.]: United States Army, n.d., Printed close score; 10 p. (Box-folder 28/1)
  - Army Service Forces. Hymns from home. {S.l.]: United States Army, n.d., Hymn text; 7 p.; (2 copies) (Box-folder 28/1)
  - Brahms, Johannes. Konzert für Violine und Orchester, D-dur, op. 77, Positive photostat of original manuscript, full score with corrections by Joseph Joachim; 106 p.; Negative photostat of original manuscript, solo violin part; 12 p.; Positive photostat of printed full score (Leipzig: Breitkopf & Härtel, n.d.); 34 p.; Laid in: Positive photostat of manuscript poem; 1 p.; Laid in: Negative photostat of article on music from Progress, April 19, 1879; 1 p.; Laid in: Negative photostat of article on music and musicology from Encyclopaedia of the Social Sciences, undated; 5 p.; Laid in: Typescript of Brahms References; 1 p. (original and carbon). (Box-folder 33/6)
  - Church, Frank. Passacaglia, 1943, Holograph manuscript in ink; [4] p. (Box-folder 28/2)
  - Crumb, George. Ancient voices of children. New York: C. F. Peters Corporation, 1971, Printed full score; [3], 8 p.; Laid in: complimentary card from C. F. Peters Corporation, annotated. (Box-folder 33/7)
  - Dallapiccola, Luigi. Parole di San Paolo, 1964, Holograph manuscript in ink and pencil; [2], 16 p.; On t.p.: "Offro questo autografo al Dr. Harold Spivacke—[?]" (Box-folder 28/3)
  - Gershwin, George. Two waltzes in C. New York: Warner Bros. Publications Inc., 1971., Piano solo; 7 p.; On verso of cover page: "For Rose Marie S. — With appreciation — And affection — From Ira G. Feb. 2, 1972." (Box-folder 28/4)
  - Harris, Roy. Contemporary folk song, undated, Holograph manuscript in pencil; 1 p. (Box-folder 33/8)
  - Malipiero, Gian Francesco. 7° quartet (Quartet, strings, no. 7). Milano: G. Ricordi & C., 1951, Printed miniature score; [2], 19 p.; Inscribed by composer, 1951. (Box-folder 28/5)
  - Malipiero, Gian Francesco. Ricercari per andici instrumenti, 1951, Holograph manuscript in pencil and ink; [1], 53 p.; On t.p.: "To Dr. Harold Spivacke, In memory of a successful collaboration in proof of a sincere friendship," signed by composer, 11 Aug. 1951.; Laid in: autograph signed letter to Dr. Spivacke, 14 Aug. 1951; 1 p.; Laid in: autograph signed envelope. (Box-folder 28/6)
  - Malipiero, Riccardo. Canone infinito. Milano: All'Insegna del Pesce d'Oro, 1969, Printed score for keyboard; [2], 5 p.; At beginning: "Per le nozze di Barbara Malipiero e Sante Cesqui, Milano, 13 ottobre 1969." (Box-folder 28/7)
  - Malipiero, Riccardo. A very short prelude to the next 100 years of Harold Spivacke, 1969, Holograph manuscript in ink; 1 p.; At end: Silver Spring, 13 July 1969.; Laid in: envelope with artwork. (Box-folder 28/8)